# Michael Delaney

1020 NE 63<sup>rd</sup> St #205, Seattle, WA 98115 mdelaney@utexas.edu 512-666-4718 github.com/MikeDelaney

# **Objective**

I love helping others accomplish difficult tasks. I find ways to improve existing processes and exploit opportunities for automation. I want to use my skills as a software developer and Python specialist to extend my track record in this area.

### **Skills**

- Python
- TDD
- BDD
- HTML

- Django
- Flask
- Fabric
- Boto

- AJAX
- JavaScript/JQuery
- Agile Workflow
- CSS

# Experience

Epicor Software – Austin, TX (1999 – 2014)

#### **Information Conversion Specialist** (2002 – 2014)

- Developed processes and tools which automated catalog production, increasing production rate from 60 files per month to consistently over 400.
- Reverse-engineered replacement for catalog interchange program, streamlining work flow and cutting per-file processing time from 30 minutes to an average of 30 seconds.
- Created and maintained user documentation for new processing tools.
- Trained California, Texas, and Ireland staff in use of new processing tools and procedures.
- Converted automotive aftermarket parts data into format compatible with electronic catalog software.
- Assisted coworkers with procedures, error resolution, and automating repetitive tasks.
- Assisted product development team with design and testing of new software.

## **Product Support Specialist – JCON** (2000 – 2002)

- Resolved hardware and software issues with UNIX based multi-user auto parts store systems.
- Supported point-of-sale, inventory, accounting, and catalog software, as well as relational databases and network communications.
- Consistently maintained one of the highest first call resolution rates on my team.
- Received customer service award for work with large national account.

## **Product Support Specialist – Service Expert** (1999 – 2000)

- Resolved issues and questions concerning operation of Windows based automotive service dealer systems.
- Supported point-of-sale and catalog software.
- Worked with product development team to support alpha release of updated software package.
- Created detailed troubleshooting instructions for hardware and software issues.

#### **Education**

Code Fellows - Seattle, WA, Certificate awarded July 2014

Python Development Accelerator

University of Texas at Austin – Austin, TX

Studied Aerospace Engineering and Economics